cagora.com 2008-09-26

# USA Privacy

**About Cagora**

Cagora is an online service made up of a network of Local and Special Interest communities designed to make it easy to share information & network with friends, family, business and people around you. Cagora users are able to view other people's profiles, communicate and network with others, create and share information such as blogs, articles, photos, videos and reviews, and find products and services locally and around the world.

Cagora understands that our members may not want their information being readily available to other Cagora users, and we want to provide you with the privacy tools necessary to control how and with whom you share that information. That is why we give our members control over their privacy settings, allowing users to set privacy around user-created circles of friends.

Cagora is as concerned about your privacy as you are. If you have any questions concerning this privacy policy, please email us at [privacy@cagora.com](mailto:privacy@cagora.com)

**Purpose**

The purpose of Cagora's Privacy Policy is to clearly and concisely explain to you how we collect and use the personal information you decide to share, who may use Cagora, and to help you make informed decisions when using Cagora, located at www.Cagora.com and all directly associated domains (collectively, "Cagora" or "Website").

By accessing and using the Cagora Network, you are agreeing with, and accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

**Collection of Information**

Each time you visit Cagora you are providing us with two types of information:

  1. Information you choose to share (personal details, information you create and share)
  2. Information collected by the Cagora website when it (the website) interacts with you (including IP addresses & geographical information).

By registering with Cagora, you may also provide us with personal information about yourself, such as your name, personal address, email address, instant messenger information, telephone number(s), gender, schools, business name(s) and any other personal information that you may choose to provide to us.

Each time you enter Cagora, we collect your browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all Cagora visitors and is not shared with third parties.

When you use Cagora, you may set up your personal profile, network with friends and like-minded individuals, send and receive messages, browse and search for information, participate in discussions and send information through various channels. Cagora may collect this information to ensure we can provide you with quality services and personalized features. When users update their information, Cagora may keep a backup copy of the prior version for a reasonable period of time to enable reversion to the prior version of that information if necessary.

You agree that any information you post on the Cagora Network is done at your own risk. Whilst we have privacy guidelines in place, please be aware that no security or privacy measure is completely perfect. Cagora cannot control the actions of other users with whom you may choose to share your pages and information. Therefore, Cagora cannot and does not guarantee that information users post on the Website will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. You understand and acknowledge that copies of information posted by users may remain viewable in archived pages or if other users have copied or stored your User Content.

Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on Cagora is a violation of the Cagora Terms of Service and should be reported to [privacy@Cagora.com](mailto:privacy@cagora.com).

**Use of Information Obtained by Cagora**

By registering with Cagora and creating your user profile, you acknowledge that your profile information may be viewable to other users of the Cagora Network. Your profile information, as well as your name, email and photo, may be displayed to people in the networks specified in your privacy settings. 

Cagora may use your personal information to make your experience with Cagora more personal, such as using your name to welcome you after logging in. Cagora also uses your personal information for features such as the Cagora Affiliate Program, Local Worlds and Worlds of Interest.

Cagora may send you, via email, announcements from time to time regarding the general operation of the Cagora Website. For example; if you refer a new user through the Cagora Affiliate Program, you may receive an email informing you of the new registration.

You may choose to opt out of such emails, although Cagora reserves the right to send important notices about the running of the Cagora Network or your account to you even after you opt out of notifications.

Cagora may use information in your profile without identifying you as an individual to third parties. We do this to ensure we offer quality services targeted to you, the user. For example; we may collect and share information about communities you are involved in to advertisers, to ensure you see Website content that is of more value to you.

We do not provide your contact information to third party marketers without your permission. We will only share your information if:

  1. It is deemed necessary in order to offer a service
  2. It is permitted by yourself
  3. We are legally required to do so

**Use Of Cookies**

The Cagora website(s) use cookies to store visitors' preferences and to record session information. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. Cagora makes use of cookies to ensure visitors are not repeatedly offered the same advertisements, to track session information for use with the Cagora Affiliate Program, and to customize advertising and web page content based on browser type, geographical location and user profile information. You may be able to configure your browser to accept, reject or alert you when a cookie is set. Cagora suggests that you enable cookies for the Cagora website(s) to get the most out of the Cagora Network.   
Please note that Cagora may allow third party advertisers who are advertising on the Cagora Website(s) to set and access their cookies on your computer. Advertisers' use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, and are not covered by the Cagora Privacy Policy.

**Forums, Blogs and Chat Rooms**

Cagora features many Web2.0 services that allow content to be transmitted to other users. Please be aware that content sent though forums, blogs and chat rooms are not secure and any information may be accessed by other users of the Cagora Network. 

**Persons Under Age 14**

Cagora does not permit any persons under the age of 14 to join or participate in the Cagora Network. Cagora does not knowingly or willingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 14, nor does Cagora knowingly or willingly allow such persons to register. If you are under the age or 14, please do not attempt to register for membership at Cagora or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No persons under age the age of 14 may provide any personal information to or on Cagora. 

In the event that Cagora learns that information has been collected from persons under the age of 14 without parental consent, all information pertaining to that individual(s) will be deleted immediately. 

If you believe Cagora has information from or about a person under the age of 14, please contact us at [privacy@Cagora.com](mailto:privacy@cagora.com).

**Parental Consent For Minors**

Cagora recommends that minors aged over 14 request consent from their parents or guardians before registering an account at Cagora.

**Links To Third Party Websites And Services**

Cagora may contain links to websites outside of the Cagora Network. We take no responsibility for the practices of these websites. We suggest that all users read the privacy policies of third party websites before sharing their personal information on or with them. 

The Cagora Privacy Policy applies solely to the Cagora website(s) and associated domain(s).

**Advertisements**

Advertisements displayed on the Cagora Website(s) may at times be delivered directly from the third party advertisers' website. Such advertisements may contain cookies to collect information such as your IP address and geographical information. They may also use web scripts such as JavaScript and flash to measure the response to their advertisements and personalize their advertisements to you, the user. Cagora does not have control over third party advertisers' tracking policies and such advertisers are not covered under the Cagora Privacy Policy. Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information stored on Cagora unless you choose to share it with them.

**Security**

Cagora will always take appropriate precautions to protect your information. All information is stored on secure servers and behind firewalls. Cagora may at times make use of Secure Socket layer technology (SSL) to protect your private information during transmissions of data (such as Credit Card payments). 

If you have any questions about the security of the Cagora Website, please contact us at [privacy@cagora.com](mailto:privacy@cagora.com)

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

From time to time we may make changes to the Cagora Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy at any time. You are bound by any minor changes to the policy when you access the Cagora Website(s) after those changes have been posted. If however changes to this policy affect our user's personal information or the way we deal with that information, we will notify by posting a notice on our Website for 30 days before the change will take place.

**Contacting Cagora**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us at [privacy@cagora.com](mailto:privacy@cagora.com).
